var questions = [{
	"question": "How many realms of reality exists in the universe?",
	"option1": "One",
	"option2": "Five",
	"option3": "Twelve",
	"option4": "Two",
	"answer":  "4"
}, {
	"question": "What are names of these realms?",
	"option1": "Heaven and Earth realms",
	"option2": "Spiritual and Physical realms",
	"option3": "Celestial and Terrestrial realms",
	"option4": "Light and darkness realms",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "Which of these realms has more influence and power?",
	"option1": "Heaven realm",
	"option2": "Physical realm",
	"option3": "Spiritual realm",
	"option4": "Earth realm",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "Who is more powerful among these?",
	"option1": "Man",
	"option2": "Angel Michael",
	"option3": "Seraphim",
	"option4": "Lucifer",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "Who is more powerful among these?",
	"option1": "Holy Spirit",
	"option2": "Jesus Christ",
	"option3": "God",
	"option4": "All the above",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "What qualifies a man to be a citizen of heaven?",
	"option1": "Going to Church",
	"option2": "Being Born again",
	"option3": "Being baptized in church",
	"option4": "Being good",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "What is the Gospel?",
	"option1": "A declaration of faith",
	"option2": "Preaching the goodness",
	"option3": "Message about the coming, death and resurrection of Jesus Christ",
	"option4": "A church fellowship",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "What is the Great Commission?",
	"option1": "The charge to preach the gospel worldwide",
	"option2": "The One World Government",
	"option3": "Branch of United Nations",
	"option4": "Money received on work done",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "Who is to be most feared by man?",
	"option1": "Lucifer",
	"option2": "Demons",
	"option3": "Armed Robbers",
	"option4": "God",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "What is the greatest trait that God desires all men to have?",
	"option1": "Consistency",
	"option2": "Love",
	"option3": "Kindness",
	"option4": "Giving",
	"answer": "2"
}]
